games4king.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy - Games4King - New Best Escape Games Every Day

This Privacy Statement applies to the web sites and mobile applications provided by Games4King (collectively, “we”, “our”, or “us”). This Privacy Statement governs your use of our Sites and Apps, regardless of how you access or use them. By “Sites”, we mean any website or URL of ours that we have linked to this Privacy Statement and all features, applications, content, and downloads that are operated by us and that are available through the Sites, and by “Mobile Apps” and “Apps”, we mean our products and services that we make available via mobile telecommunications platforms and/or through social networking platforms or app stores, if you are visiting the Sites, please also review the Sites’ Term of Service.

We want you and your family to have fun surfing all our Sites and using our Apps, and urge you and your family to follow common sense whenever disclosing personal information – on this Site or anywhere else.

We encourage you to review our complete Privacy Statement in detail, as it includes important information, but provided is a short summary for convenience.

Apps

When downloading an App (or using an App that relies on online features made available through your mobile platform), the app store will collect certain device and app-related information. We do not control the data collection or privacy practices of those stores. You should review the privacy policy and terms of use of any mobile application store before downloading or using any app and review and use available controls and settings on your device to reflect your preferences.

 Website and Mobile App Analytics

We or our agents and service partners may use cookies and web beacons to analyze the effectiveness of our Sites, services and Apps. This typically involves collecting your IP address or UDID and information on your activities, like the sites you visit or frequency of use of an App. We require these providers to commit to maintaining the anonymity of this information. You may be able to opt out of data collection or use by some third party analytics companies who work with us. Contact us if you would like information on our third party analytics service providers.

### CHILDREN

WE DO NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER 13.

We take many special precautions to protect the privacy of children under 13.

· At our websites through our apps intended for children, we do not collect personal contact information (like full name, birthdate, phone number or home address) from children without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, except in limited circumstances authorized by law.

· We collect some information (like IP address, mobile device UDID, operating system, etc.) automatically and use technology like cookies to provide functionality and support our operations. We do not permit interest-based advertising on Sites or Apps directed to children under 13 or where we have actual knowledge that a child is under 13.

· We do not ask for more personal information than is necessary for a child to participate in an activity.

· We take steps to prevent children from posting or publicly disclosing personal contact information.

· Parents can ask us to update or delete their children’s information.

We use technology, like cookies, to recognize visitors by their user name when they revisit our Site and to screen for age in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). We may also use technology for similar purposes in our Apps.

We also use technology to facilitate the ability to play games, to recognize returning visitors, for research, and for other purposes, including to screen under-age visitors from certain features or areas intended for older visitors, and to collect certain information automatically. We require our advertising service partners to comply with self-regulatory guidelines on targeted advertising. We do not permit interest-based advertising on Sites directed to children under 13 or where we have actual knowledge that a child is under 13.

### WHAT WE COLLECT – ADULTS AND TEENS

We sometimes collect information from adults and teens to serve your needs, manage our content and advertising, operate efficiently, and improve our products and services.

· We may collect personal contact information, like e-mail address or phone number, from consumers 13 or older when voluntarily submitted, including when needed to fulfill transactions. Registration may be required to use some Sites, services or Apps.

· We may obtain information from commercial sources and combine it with information we have collected.

· Certain information may be collected automatically at our Sites or Apps, like your IP address, UDID, browser setting, operating system, referring domain, language preferences, mobile carrier if you are using a mobile device, general location (e.g., zip code, but not specific address without consent) and other information.

· Third parties may also collect certain information via our Sites or Apps.

### USER-GENERATED

You may be able to post or upload content, like comments, reviews, photos, etc. Registration may be required.

### COOKIES AND TECHNOLOGY

You may be able to post or upload content, like comments, reviews, photos, etc. Registration may be required.

· Our Sites, services and Apps use technology, like cookies and web beacons, to manage registrations or access to certain features, store your settings and preferences, conduct age-screening, offer you personalized content, shop, help us understand the features that appeal to visitors, and manage advertising, among other things.

· We also work with third parties who offer analytics or deliver targeted ads online or through Apps. They use technology and collect device identifiers, such as your IP address or mobile UDID, and information on your activities, to do so. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads but will still see ads, although they may be less relevant to you.

· Tools are available to help you control some of these technologies.

· Our and its agents or service providers or business partners may receive and store certain information automatically when you visit our Sites, use an online service or download or use a mobile App. This may include information on your browser type and operating system, the pages that you view, referring sites (sites you visited before you came to our site and sites you go to after you visit our site), IP addresses, or unique device identifiers associated with mobile devices, smart phones, etc. This information allows us to count the total number of “hits” on our Sites or installation and frequency of use of our Apps.

· We collect certain information using technology, like cookies and pixel tags. We may also use “Flash” cookies in connection with some games or other content to store game and activity progress for the Flash player or to store bandwidth information for the performance of the Flash player. The information stored in any Flash cookie deployed on this Site does not include your name.

· Third party analytics and advertising networks also use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, clear GIFs and other technology to collect certain information automatically. Advertising networks may use this information to serve you targeted ads for products and services that, based on your activities, are likely to be of interest to you (“interest-based advertising”). We do not permit interest-based advertising on Sites directed to children under 13 or where we have actual knowledge that a child is under 13.

· Other business partners, like social media sites, may also use cookies and similar technology to collect certain information about your visits to our Sites through social media plug-ins. You may have the option to log in to one of our websites using your social media user name and password; if so, the social media operator (e.g., Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) may be able to link your activities at our Site to your registration information.

· Find out more about these technologies and how you can control their use below.

Cookies

A “cookie” is a small file that does not contain personally identifiable information and is saved on your computer or mobile device. Cookies help improve your user experience, and allow us to analyze our Sites and Apps and manage our advertising.· 

· Our cookies help to give you faster access to pages you have already visited; they allow you to personalize your pages and us to customize our offerings; and they help you to participate in some activities or events on our Sites. For instance, some of our Sites have scavenger or treasure hunts, and we need to use cookies to keep track of your progress. If you leave our Site and then return, cookies will tell us what things you have already collected so that you do not have to start all over again. Cookies can also keep track of items in your shopping cart and wish list in our online stores, and may be used to help you engage in other activities, like comparison shopping.

· We also use cookies to help us figure out how many people visit our Sites, which of our Web pages they go to and how long they stay there. This information helps us figure out which of our Web features are successes and what Sites might need improvement. For administrative purposes, we collect IP addresses. Certain Internet service providers may assign the same IP address to many users. The IP address allows us to count the total number of “hits” on our sites. Your IP address and cookies are not connected to any personally identifiable or online contact information, like a name or email address, unless you register or order at our online stores; however, if you register at our online stores, all information we collect will be associated with your customer file.

· You can set your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or turn off all cookies (except Flash cookies – see below) through your Internet browser (e.g., Internet Explorer or Safari). Check your browser’s Help menu or your built-in mobile device settings to find out how. Some mobile devices store cookies not only in areas connected to the browser, but also in areas that are app-specific so these cookies cannot be controlled by the browser settings. Check your app settings options on your mobile device to find out how to manage or delete cookies that may be stored in these other areas.

· Please note that if you do not accept cookies, some features or activities may not be available to you.

· 

Flash cookiesFlash cookies, also known as local shared objects (“LSOs”), are built for use with Adobe® Flash® Player. LSOs act like cookies in that they store information to provide you with a more customized experience, but LSOs can store complex data that cookies cannot, and LSOs are not deleted or rejected if you set your browser to delete or reject cookies. The information stored in any LSO deployed by our Sites do not include your name. Although browser settings will not allow you to manage LSOs, you may be able to manage them in other ways. To find out more about how to manage or delete LSOs, visit [ ** _http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/articles/lso/_**](http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/articles/lso/).

Web Beacons, Pixel tags or clear GIFs

We also use other technology, called web beacons, pixel tags or clear GIFs, to provide us with other important anonymous information, such as when an e-mail has been opened. Companies that advertise on our Sites may also place web beacons in their ads to help develop statistics on the effectiveness of advertising at our Sites. We do not control web beacons in third party ads.

Location information

For some Apps or services, we or our third party service and content providers and analytics companies may collect location information, including location information provided either by a mobile device interacting with one of our Apps or associated with your IP address or WiFi network. These features might enable you to engage in activities like find a nearby store or play certain games, for example. You can generally limit or prohibit the collection of location information by using the built-in settings on your mobile device. You will typically be notified if the App or service collects location information and given a chance to agree. We do not permit collection of precise location information (actual address) in mobile Apps without your consent. Child-directed Apps do not collect precise location information.

Targeted Advertising

Our Apps may work with third party online or mobile network advertisers that use cookies, pixels, or transparent GIF files to help us manage advertising at our Sites or Apps intended for people over the age of 13, and measure its effectiveness. GIF files enable third party ad networks to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser or mobile device. The cookie may be placed by us, or by another advertiser that works with our third party network advertiser. The information that we collect and share in this fashion is de-identified and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. However, it may keep track of the sites you have visited that are associated with the ad network. This information may be used for the purpose of targeting advertisements on our Sites and other sites based on those interests, and to learn which ads bring users to our Sites. Please note: your opt-out choices are browser-specific and device-specific.

Social Media Platforms and Plugins

If you are a member of a social media network, like Facebook, a cookie may be sent to that network when you access a page of our Site or an App that links to their website through a plugin (such as Facebook’s “Like” or Google “+1” buttons), register or log into your account at their platform, or use your social media user name and password to log into our Site where you have the option to do so. That may enable them and us to link your activities with your personal registration information at their site, and may include notifying your friends or connections about your activities at our Site, and using tracking technologies to monitor your online activities in order to serve targeted ads. The social media networks’ privacy policy and terms apply to your use of their platforms. Your browser or device may allow you to block these technologies but you should visit the third party website and review their privacy policy and your registration profile or account to find out your options.

### LINKS

Our Sites or Apps may link to or use other content from the Internet, including content offered by third parties that we do not control and whose privacy and data collection practices may differ from ours. Your computer or mobile device settings may allow you to block or partially block web access, but those settings may not be effective in all cases.

### OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION ****

SECURITY

We strive to maintain the security of information but cannot guarantee that information security measures are fail-safe

OUR LOCATION; DATA TRANSFERS

This Site and the servers that make this Site available may not be located in your country of residence and are governed by U.S. laws. By using this Site, you agree to the transfer, collection, processing and use of data by this Site and us. This Site, the servers that make this Site available, and databases where we house information may not be located in your country of residence, and applicable privacy laws may differ. However, we take reasonable steps to safeguard personal information as outlined in this Privacy Statement. By using this Site, you agree to the transfer, collection, processing and use of data as set forth in this Privacy Statement, our Terms and Conditions, and any other terms provided at the time of collection. However related to mobile apps, the servers that store the data will be of the respective platforms.

Games4King.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know our choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

QUESTIONS

We strive always to be transparent and clear about our policies. Please contact us at games4kinginfo@gmail.com if you have questions.
